Guide to the Robert A. Hill Collection, 1890-2014 RL.10993
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Microfilm (MF), 1819-1987 and undated; 7; 8 boxes
  - Microfilm, 1
    - Colored American, 1915 Oct-1916 Jun (Box MF2, Reel 64)
      Vol.1, The Colored American Review, duplicate negative
    - Coolidge, Calvin, 1923 Sep 23-1924 Dec 13 (Box MF2, Reel 65)
      Series 1 91 continued - 93, Presidential Papers Microfilm
    - Coolidge, Calvin, 1925 Jan 3-1928 Jun 27 (Box MF2, Reel 66)
      Series 1 93 continued - 94, Presidential Papers Microfilm
    - Coolidge, Calvin, 1923 Nov 5-1927 Jul 11 (Box MF2, Reel 67)
      Series 1 608 continued - 686, Presidential Papers Microfilm
    - Counselor, Office of the, 1925 Aug 24-1926 Mar 19 (Box MF2, Reel 68)
      RG 59 - Office of the Counselor
    - Community Service Order (CSO) - secret and confidential files, 1935 Apr 18-1952 Oct 13 (Box MF2, Reel 69)
      Jamaica Archives and Records Dept - CNR King and Manchester Streets, Spanish Town and St. Catherine, CSO 1B/5/77 1B/5/79
    - Committee on Public Information, 1918 Apr-Aug (Box MF2, Reel 70)
      RG 63, Committee on Public Information Folders: CPI 1-A Emmett Scott, CPI 1-A5 Negroes
    - Committee on Public Information, 1918 Apr 5-Aug 1 (Box MF2, Reel 71)
      RG 63, Folders: CPI 1-A Emmett Scott, CPI 1-A5 Negroes, negative
    - Correspondence, 1924 May 22-1936 Jul 28 (Box MF2, Reel 72)
      Oxford. Bodleian Library, MS. Brit. Emp. S.23, Foreign Archives, correspondence relating to visit of SA Delegation to England, 1919-1929, Hostel for Africans in London, British Africans in Europe, etc.
    - Cuba, 1910 Apr 23-1927 Jul 21 (Box MF2, Reel 73)
      Records of the Department of State Relating to Internal Affairs of Cuba - immigration, emigration
    - Department of Justice, 1921 Mar 11-1938 Feb 5 (Box MF2, Reel 74)
      RG 60 Records of the Department of Justice Numerical File Selected File Numbers, positive, Files are: 101134, 215059, 160962, 201762/110, 72-40-1, 223955, 35-51
    - Department of Justice, 1921 Mar 11-1938 Feb 5 (Box MF2, Reel 75)
      RG 60 Records of the Department of Justice Numerical File Selected File Numbers, negative
    - Diplomatic Post Records, 1921 Sep 25-1922 Mar (Box MF2, Reel 76)
      US Diplomatic Post Records, Paris, Havana - selected miscellaneous documents
    - Dixon, Edward - The American Negro in Nineteenth-Century Scotland, 1969 May (Box MF2, Reel 77)
      Dissertation, Foreign Archives, M. Lit. 1969, Miss Marjory Carpenter Head Interlibrary loans Northwestern University Library Evanston, Illinois, 60201 USA
    - DuBois/E. Geiss, 1923 (Box MF2, Reel 78)
      Association Pan-Africaine correspondence - French language
    - Du Bois papers - Emanuel Geiss, 1897 Jun-1920 Jan (Box MF2, Reel 79)
      Reports relating to Jamaica, Jamaica Archives
    - Dunayevskaya, Raya, 1938 Dec-1956 Jul (Box MF2, Reel 80)
      Reel 1
    - Dunayevskaya, Raya, 1957 Sep 1-1975 (Box MF2, Reel 81)
      Reel 2
    - Dunayevskaya, Raya, undated (Box MF2, Reel 82)
      Reel 3
    - Dunayevskaya, Raya, 1965 Dec-1981 Feb (Box MF2, Reel 83)
      Reel 4
    - Dunayevskaya, Raya, 1955 Feb-1963 Jun (Box MF2, Reel 84)
      Reel 5
    - Dunayevskaya, Raya, 1980 Sep-1981 Jan (Box MF2, Reel 85)
      Reel 6
    - Dunayevskaya, Raya, 1987 Jun 1 (Box MF2, Reel 86)
      Reel 7
    - Fight, 1938 Apr-Jun, Aug, Oct-Nov, 1939 Jan (Box MF2, Reel 87)
      London, print negative
    - Fight, 1938 Apr-Jun, Aug, Oct-Nov, 1939 Jan (Box MF2, Reel 88)
      The British Library - Newspaper Library, positive
    - Fight, 1936 Oct-1927 Nov (Box MF2, Reel 89)
      Houghton Library
    - Fight, 1936 Oct-1927 Nov (Box MF2, Reel 90)
      Houghton Library, duplicate negative
    - Garnet, H.H., 1834 (Box MF2, Reel 91)
      London, Bodleian Library, MS. Brit. Emp. S.18, negative
    - Garvey, Marcus, 1927 Feb-1932 Aug (Box MF2, Reel 92)
      Jamaica Archives, negative
    - Garvey, Marcus, 1922 Aug 5-1944 Mar 4 (Box MF2, Reel 93)
      Newspaper clippings, petitions, Columbia University Library, duplicate negative
    - Garvey and Rastafari, 1929 Jul 1, 1930 Aug 8 (Box MF2, Reel 94)
      1. Petition re Lewis Ashenheim-Appendix A 1 July 1929, 2. Report by Overseas Section by the Central Special Intelligence Bureau, London, 3. British Legation, Panama Stuff 1911, 4. CSO Royal Commission, Appointment of 22.8.30, Jamaica Archives
    - Garvey and Rastafari, 1923 Dec-1929 Dec (Box MF2, Reel 95)
      Minutes, telegrams, correspondence, Jamaica Archives
    - Geiss, Emanuel, 1918 Jan 5-1924 Feb 15 (Box MF2, Reel 96)
      London, British Library
    - General correspondence, Records of the Second Isthmian Canal Commission, Records of the Panama Canal, Record Group 185, 1925 (Box MF2, Reel 97)
      File 61-H-2, B-00085 return to Garvey Papers
    - Green, Loraine Richardson, 1919 Jun (Box MF2, Reel 98)
      Rise of Race and Consciousness in the American Negro, University of Chicago Master's thesis
    - Gumby, Alexander, undated (Box MF2, Reel 99)
      Alexander Gumby Collection
    - Haiti, Santo Domingo, 1918 Jul-1937 Mar 14 (Box MF2, Reel 100)
      Department of State Records - Haiti, Santo Domingo
    - Helena World, 1918 Jan 1, 1918 Jun 30 (Box MF2, Reel 101)
      Vol. 70, Vol. 74
    - Hill, Professor Robert, 1953 Nov 8-1958 Feb 25 (Box MF2, Reel 102)
      Lyman-J Roe through Weaver and Org. 1953-1954
    - Hill, Professor Robert, 1951 Oct 31-1958 Apr 18 (Box MF2, Reel 103)
      Martin L King Jr. through Letters Reel 2
    - Hogg, Donald William, 1964, 1967 (Box MF2, Reel 104)
      Jamaican Religions, Ph.D. dissertation, Yale University
    - International African Opinion, 1938 Jul-Sep (Box MF2, Reel 105)
      Vol. 1 No. 1-3
    - Israel, W.E., 1928 Sep (Box MF2, Reel 106)
      The Montreal Negro Community,, MA thesis McGill University, positive
    - Izwi Lama Afrika, 1931 May 8-1932 Feb 27 (Box MF2, Reel 107)
      Izwi Lama Afrika, newspaper, The South African Library
    - Jamaica Archives, 1952 May 1-1966 Apr 22 (Box MF2, Reel 108)
      J.A. Photographs, ref. 4/77/11
    - Jamaica Times, 1909 (Box MF2, Reel 109)
      The Banana in Jamaica: Export Trade, Hart, Ansell
    - Jamaica Times, 1909 (Box MF2, Reel 110)
    - Jamaica Times, 1910 (Box MF3, Reel 111)
    - Jamaica Times, 1910 Jan 15-Aug 27 (Box MF3, Reel 112)
    - Jamaica Times, 1910 Aug 27-1921 Oct 8 (Box MF3, Reel 113)
    - Jamaica Times, 1911 (Box MF3, Reel 114)
    - Jamaica Times, 1912 Jan-Jun (Box MF3, Reel 115)
    - Jamaica Times, 1912 Jul-Dec (Box MF3, Reel 116)
    - Jamaica Times, 1912 Jan 6-Dec 21 (Box MF3, Reel 117)
    - Jamaica Times, 1912 Jan 13-1913 Aug 16 (Box MF3, Reel 118)
    - Jamaica Times, 1913 Jan-Sep (Box MF3, Reel 119)
    - Jamaica Times, 1913 Sep-1914 Nov (Box MF3, Reel 120)
    - Jamaica Times, 1913 Feb to Dec (Box MF3, Reel 121)
    - Jamaica Times, 1914 Sep 5-1917 Jul 7 (Box MF3, Reel 122)
    - Jamaica Times, 1914 (Box MF3, Reel 123)
    - Jamaica Times, 1915 Jan 9-Nov 27 (Box MF3, Reel 124)
    - Jamaica Times, 1916 (Box MF3, Reel 125)
    - Jamaica Times, 1917 Jul 7-1919 Jul 5 (Box MF3, Reel 126)
    - Jamaica Times, 1957 Jun-1958 Nov (Box MF3, Reel 127)
      duplicate
    - Jamaica Times, 1958 Nov-1960 Aug (Box MF3, Reel 128)
    - Jamaica Times, 1960 Aug-1961 Nov (Box MF3, Reel 129)
    - Japanese, undated (Box MF3, Reel 130)
    - Japanese, undated (Box MF3, Reel 131)
    - Kanawha and G.W. Goethals, undated (Box MF3, Reel 132)
      Records of U.S. Shipping Board RG 32 Records of Bureau of Marine Inspection and Navigation RG 41
    - Knox, A.J. Graham, 1962 (Box MF3, Reel 133)
      Race Relations in Jamaica, 1833-1958 PhD dissertation University of Florida
    - Le Progres Colonial, 1921 Jan 30-Sep 8 (Box MF3, Reel 134)
      L'Aulnior, Colonial Belge
    - Leader to be placed on Marcus Garvey microfilm, 1977 Nov. 23 (Box MF3, Reel 135)
      General Services Administration correspondence
    - League of Nations, 1919 Mar 24-1935 Jul 29 (Box MF3, Reel 136)
      3272 Guardian V. 11-12 Oct 20, 1958-Oct 3, 1960 Reel 6
    - League of Nations Archives, undated (Box MF3, Reel 137)
    - Les Continents, 1924 Jun 15-Dec 15 (Box MF3, Reel 138)
      Es Continents
    - Liberia, 1920 Feb18-1921 Dec 30 (Box MF3, Reel 139)
      Diplomatic Correspondance from the United States Legation to Liberia and US Consulate in Port of Spain, Trinidad. British West Indies, negative
    - Lisbon, 1909 Jul 6-1921 May 26 (Box MF3, Reel 140)
      Fornal Colonias, newspaper
    - Mahania Kimpianga II, 1975 May 29 (Box MF3, Reel 141)
      Degree Date: 1975, Cat. No: 7528233
    - Malawi National Archive, 1920 Apr 22-1938 Sep (Box MF3, Reel 142)
      Zomba, Malawi
    - Manoedi, M.M., undated (Box MF3, Reel 143)
      Garvey and Africa, New York
    - Marcus Garvey vs. U.S.A., 1924 Feb. 27 (Box MF3, Reel 144)
      Records of the U.S. Supreme Court
    - Marcus Garvey vs. U.S.A., 1923 Jun 21 (Box MF3, Reel 145)
    - Ministere Des Affaires Estrangers Directions Des Affaires Politique et Commerciales 27, 1919 Jan 25-1939 Mar 17 (Box MF3, Reel 146)
      Serie K Carton 4, Dossier 1, Questions Generales, Congres Pan-African, Propagande Marcus Garvey, Attitude Des Americans, Foreign Office Directorate of Political undated Commercial Affairs
    - Ministere Des Affaires Estrangers Directions Des Affaires Politique et Commerciales 27, 1919 Jan 25-1939 Mar 16 (Box MF3, Reel 147)
      Serie K Carton 4, Dossier 1 (Questions Generales, Congres Pan-African, Propagande Marcus Garvey, Attitude Des Americans), Foreign Office Directorate of Political undated Commercial Affairs, Duplicate
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1916-1917 (Box MF3, Reel 148)
      Miscellaneous Articles 1916-17
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1914-1917, 1918 (Box MF3, Reel 149)
      African Times and Orient Revision, London
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1899 Jan-Mar (Box MF3, Reel 150)
      Daily Gleaner, Kingston
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1899 Apr-Jun (Box MF3, Reel 151)
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1893-1917 (Box MF3, Reel 152)
      Extracts from Various Jamaican Newspapers: Daily Chronicle, Daily Gleaner, Tri-Weekly Newsletter, Daily Telegraph, Gall's Daily Newsletter, Telegraph and Guardian, 12/1/73, PS 209865
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1897-1902, 1905-1912, 1915-1934 (Box MF3, Reel 153)
      Extracts from various newspapers 1897-1902: The Daily Gleaner, Extracts from Jamaica Times 1905-12, Extracts from various newspapers 1915-1934 The Gold Coast Independent, Jamaica Times, The Daily Chronicle (JA)
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1897-1914 (Box MF3, Reel 154)
      Extracts from the Daily Gleaner newspaper 1897-1914
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1904-1933 (Box MF3, Reel 155)
      Extracts from Jamaica Times and Daily Gleaner newspapers 1904-1933
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1908 Oct 3-1909 Apr 3 (Box MF3, Reel 156)
      Jamaica Tribun, Kingston, First Received 3 Oct 1908 to 3 Apr 1909
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1907 Nov 2-Dec 28 (Box MF3, Reel 157)
      The Jamaican, Kingston, positive
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1907 Nov 2-Dec 28 (Box MF3, Reel 158)
      The Jamaican
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1920 (Box MF3, Reel 159)
      Library of Congress Misc. Collection of Radical Newspapers, NW 1920 May 1, May 8, Jun 19, Jun 26, Jul 317,31, Aug 14, Aug 21
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1924-43 (Box MF3, Reel 160)
      Miscellaneous Newspapers: Plain Talk, Negro Voice, The Herald 1924-43
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1932-1933 (Box MF3, Reel 161)
      The New Jamaican #15 beginning of tape-full page
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1933 Feb 4-Sep 9 (Box MF3, Reel 162)
      The New Jamaican, 1933 Sep 15: Letter to subscribers
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, undated (Box MF3, Reel 163)
      Our Own, Jamaica
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1935 May-1936 Dec (Box MF3, Reel 164)
      Plain Talk
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, undated (Box MF3, Reel 165)
      Plain Talk, negative
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1935 May-Dec (Box MF4, Reel 166)
    - Miscellaneous newspapers, 1937, 1935, 1936 (Box MF4, Reel 167)
      Plain Talk, Jamaica
    - Mistakes of Dr. W.E.B. Du Bois, 1921 (Box MF4, Reel 168)
      Sheppard, Wheeler, 2 Vols.- Pittsburgh, 1921
    - Mistakes of Dr. W.E.B. Du Bois, 1921 (Box MF4, Reel 169)
    - National Archives of Rhodesia, 1935 Dec-1938 Feb 7 (Box MF4, Reel 171)
    - National Archives of Rhodesia, undated (Box MF4, Reel 172)
    - National Diet Library, Japan, undated (Box MF4, Reel 173)
    - National Diet Library, Japan, undated (Box MF4, Reel 174)
    - National Film Board, 1920 Nov 13 (Box MF4, Reel 175)
      South Africa Archives, Foreign Archives, SAGA, Contains Negro World 1920 Nov 13
    - The Negro, 1918 Aug 7-1923 Jul 25 (Box MF4, Reel 176)
      National Civic Federation The Negro, negative
    - Negro Subversive, 1917-1941 (Box MF4, Reel 177)
      M.I.D. Record Cards, Negro Subersive
    - Negro Worker Material, 1931 (Box MF4, Reel 178)
    - New York Age, 1916 Oct 5-1918 Dec 28 (Box MF4, Reel 179)
    - New York Age, 1919 Jan 4-1921 (Box MF4, Reel 180)
    - New York Age, 1921 Feb 12-1924 Jan 12 (Box MF4, Reel 181)
    - New York Age, 1924 Jan 19-1926 Dec 25 (Box MF4, Reel 182)
    - New York Age, 1927 Jan 1-1928 Dec 29 (Box MF4, Reel 183)
    - New York Age, 1929 Jan 5-1930 Dec 27 (Box MF4, Reel 184)
    - New York Age, 1931 Jan 3-1932 Dec 31 (Box MF4, Reel 185)
    - New York Age, 1936 Sep 5-1938 May 28 (Box MF4, Reel 186)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1922 Nov-1925 Jul (Box MF4, Reel 187)
      Edgar Grey Editorials: May 13, May 27, Jun 3, Jun 10
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1925 Jul-1926 Sep (Box MF4, Reel 188)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1926 Sep-1927 Aug (Box MF4, Reel 189)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1927 Aug-1928 Aug (Box MF4, Reel 190)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1928 Aug-1929 Sep (Box MF4, Reel 191)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1929 Sep-1930 Aug (Box MF4, Reel 192)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1930 Aug-1931 Dec (Box MF4, Reel 193)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1931 Dec-1932 Dec (Box MF4, Reel 194)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1933 Jan-1934 Feb (Box MF4, Reel 195)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1934 Feb-1935 Mar (Box MF4, Reel 196)
    - New York Amsterdam News, 1935 Apr-1936 Apr (Box MF4, Reel 197)
    - New York News, 1921-1927 (Box MF4, Reel 198)
      3 issues
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 199)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom III C.53, French typescript, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 200)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom V, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 201)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom III C.144, 61, C.95, 89, 65, 67, Slotfom V C.11, 21
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 202)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom III C. 136, 47, 78, 75, 73, 72, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 203)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom 88 III C. 84 (2), C. 151, C. 149, B241-1 Diane Hill, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 204)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom III C. 34, 36, 50, 3, 5, 112, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 205)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom III C.53, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 206)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom III C. 24, 11, 37, 45, 2, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 207)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom III C. 86, C. 2415, C. 2416, C. 29, C.1, C.58, C.92, C.84 (2), B241-2 Diane Hill, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - Northeastern University Boston, undated (Box MF4, Reel 208)
      Ministère des Colonies. Service de liaison avec les orginaires des territories français d'outre-mer (Slotfom), Slotfom V C.10, Colonial Office liaison service from the French territories overseas (Slotfom)
    - NY Times, 1921 Feb 28 (Box MF4, Reel 209)
    - Panama Canal Company, 1920 (Box MF4, Reel 210)
      Strike of Silver Employees in 1920, File No. PCC-2-P-59/20, 8 volumes
    - Panama R.P., 1920 (Box MF4, Reel 211)
    - Pfeffer, Paula F, 1980 (Box MF4, Reel 212)
      A. Philip Randolph: A Case Study in Black Leadership, 1980 Degree Date
    - Philadelphia Tribune, 1917 Oct 6-1920 Apr 3 (Box MF4, Reel 213)
    - Philadelphia Tribune, 1920 Apr 10-1924 Jan 12 (Box MF4, Reel 214)
      Dec 1921-Nov 1922 MISSING!!
    - Philadelphia Tribune, 1924 Jan 26-1925 Mar 28 (Box MF4, Reel 215)
    - Pittsburgh Courier, 1937 (Box MF4, Reel 216)
    - Plaintalk, 1937 Jan-1939 Feb (Box MF5, Reel 217)
    - Public Record Office (PRO), London, 1838 (Box MF5, Reel 218)
      Jamaica
    - Propaganda, undated (Box MF5, Reel 219)
      Military Intelligence (Naval Records Collection) WP Enemy Propaganda, MSC. Propaganda in its military and legal aspects, negative
    - The Public Opinion Weekly Journal, 1917 Aug 12-Aug 8 (Box MF5, Reel 220)
    - Radical Black Activities in U.S., Carribbean, Comintern (Box MF5, Reel 221)
      Department of State Records. National Archives--[Radical Black Activities in U.S., Carribbean, Comintern]
    - Registro de Asociaciones, undated (Box MF5, Reel 222)
      Cuban National Archive, Fondo: Registro de Asociaciones, Legajos: 306 Exp: 8892, 388 Exp: 11640, Fotogramas: 159
    - Repercussions Des Congres Panafricain, undated (Box MF5, Reel 223)
    - Rhodesia National Archives, 1922-1939 (Box MF5, Reel 224)
      Rhodesia National Archives, S 138/55 1922-33, S 542/78A 1933-39, negative
    - Santo Domingo 1914-1920, 1920-1921 (Box MF5, Reel 225)
      Office of Naval Intelligence Miscellaneous Records, Military Gov. of Santo Domingo 1914-1920 (Contains Negro World, Sep 11, 1920, Oct 23, 1920, Feb 5, 1921, Mar 5, 1921, Oct 29, 1921
    - Scholes, Theo E.S. - Sugar and the West Indies, undated (Box MF5, Reel 226)
      London. British Library
    - Scholes, Theophilus E. Samuel, undated (Box MF5, Reel 227)
      Martin Luther King, Jr. Library - Doc. Project Scholes, Theophilus E. Samuel Glimpse of the Ages Vols. 1 and 2
    - Schomburg Collection, undated (Box MF5, Reel 228)
      Calender of the Manuscripts Schomburg Collection
    - Searbrook, John Howard, 1980 (Box MF5, Reel 229)
      Black and White Unite: The Career of Frank R. Crosswaith, 1980 Degree Date
    - Second-Class Mailing Privileges, undated (Box MF5, Reel 230)
      Records of Post Office Dept. (Record Group 28) Series No.40, Denial of Second-Class Mailing Privileges B-123 The Crisis
    - Archives Nationales du Senegal, undated (Box MF5, Reel 231)
      Archives Naturales du Senegal
    - Sinn Fein - ethics, constitution, policy, catechism, in tabloid form, etc. (Box MF5, Reel 232)
      National Library of Ireland, negative
    - The Sixth and Seventh Books of Moses, undated (Box MF5, Reel 233)
    - Shipping Board, undated (Box MF5, Reel 234)
      Records of the United States Shipping Board and of the Bureau of Navigation relating to Marcus Garvey, RG's 32 & 41, Roll 1
    - Shipping Board, undated (Box MF5, Reel 235)
      Records of the United States Shipping Board and of the Bureau of Navigation relating to Marcus Garvey, RG's 32 & 41, Roll 2
    - Sosna, Morton, undated (Box MF5, Reel 236)
      Negroes and the Wilson Years 1912-1916: Politics of Race during the Progressive Era, MA thesis U of Wisconsin, positive
    - The Spokesman - NY, 1925 Jan-1927 Aug (Box MF5, Reel 237)
      The Spokesman (NY) Jan 1925-Aug 1927 (Incomplete) Vol. 1-3
    - State Dept Decimal File, 1985 Dec 23 (Box MF5, Reel 238)
      State Dept Decimal File, RG 59, B9
    - Tracy, Alfred Ernest - The Negro Problem, undated (Box MF5, Reel 239)
      London. British Library, negative
    - Universal Negro Reel 1, 1918-1959 (Box MF5, Reel 240)
      Box 1-Box 4, 2A.154 10014 Pos Exp. 1548, Stack Annex E 185.5 U54 reel 1
    - Universal Negro Reel 2, 1918-1959 (Box MF5, Reel 241)
      Box 5-Box 6, 2A 154 9817 Pos Exp 1330, Stack Annex E 185.5 U54 reel 2
    - Universal Negro Reel 3, 1918-1959 (Box MF5, Reel 242)
      Box 7-Box 9, 2A 154 9514 Pos Exp 1282, Stack Annex E 185.5 U54 reel 3
    - Universal Negro Reel 4, 1918-1959 (Box MF5, Reel 243)
      Box 10-Box 12, 12 C 81 to be continued, 2A.154 9217 Pos Exp 1345, Stack Anenx E 185.5 U54 reel 4
    - Universal Negro Reel 5, 1918-1959 (Box MF5, Reel 244)
      Box 12 E 82 continued-Box 14 E 202 to be continued, 2A 154 9517 Pos Exp 1346, Stack Annex E 185.5 U54 reel 5
    - Universal Negro Reel 6, 1918-1959 (Box MF5, Reel 245)
      Box 14 F 1 continued -Box 16 H 10, 2A 154 8017 Pos Exp 892, Stack Annex E 185.5 U54 reel 6
    - UNIA File on Film, 1919 (Box MF5, Reel 246)
      UNIA File on Film which includes excerpts from NW for 1919, Mainly on Black Star Line, No Division Reports, NY5 Legislature Committee to Investigate Seditious Activities (Lusk com't)
    - Universal African Improvement Association, 1929-77 (Box MF5, Reel 247)
      Toronto Records, (Black)
    - The Union, 1918 Oct 5-1923 Sep 22 (Box MF5, Reel 248)
    - Unknown, undated (Box MF5, Reel 249)
      Eastman Kodak Company, 29-17
    - Unknown, undated (Box MF5, Reel 250)
    - U.S. vs. Mitti Maud Lena Gordon, undated (Box MF5, Reel 251)
      Records of the U.S. Supreme Court, Reel 1 Appellate Case No. 30924 and No. 479, U.S. vs Mitti Maud Lena Gordon
    - Voice of Missions, 1893 Jan-1900 Dec (Box MF5, Reel 252)
      Voice of Missions
    - Voice of the Negro, 1904-1907 (Box MF5, Reel 253)
      Voice of the Negro, Vol.1-4, No. 2
    - Voice of the People, 1901 Feb 1-1904 Feb 1 (Box MF5, Reel 254)
      The Voice of the People
    - West Indian - Mail Edition, 1918 Nov 8-1920 Dec (Box MF5, Reel 255)
      positive
    - West Indies Reaction, undated (Box MF5, Reel 256)
      Public Record Office, London, negative, 1B/5 Secret Confidential Papers
    - Wilson, Woodrow, undated (Box MF5, Reel 257)
      Woodrow Wilson Papers, negative
    - The Workman, 1921 Oct 8-1924 Apr 12 (Box MF5, Reel 258)
      The Workman Apr 12, 1919-Apr 12, 1924, Reel 2 Oct 8, 1921-Apr 12, 1924, American Periodicals
    - Yard, Lionel, undated (Box MF5, Reel 259)
      Department of Justice (Lionel Yard)
    - Yard, Lionel, undated (Box MF5, Reel 260)
      Department of Justice (Lionel Yard), negative
    - Zimbabwe Archives, 1922-1933, 1933-1939 (Box MF5, Reel 261)
    - Universal Negro Reel 6, 1918-1959 (Box MF6, Reel 245)
    - UNIA File on Film, 1919 (Box MF6, Reel 246)
    - Universal African Improvement Association, 1929-77 (Box MF6, Reel 247)